Heat. Heat.
Junior. Hey, what's wrong?
Probably stress. Too many assignment.
>> You have been overworking yourself,
Daniel. You okay to walk? Sit first.
Sit.
If something happened to me, I don't
even have protection. Bro, don't joke
like that.
>> Guys, my dad asked me if I have
insurance, but I said I will get it
after graduation.
And if something happened before that,
>> medical bills, accidents, all need
money.
>> Oh, I thought insurance was for rich
people.
>> Hey, no, no, no, no, no.
Or maybe it's for people who plan early.
>> A few moments later.
Uh my friend and I want to know more
about your insurance company policy. So
can you explain it to us?
>> Okay. Uh I can uh meet me around 9:00
a.m. at the meeting room. Okay.
>> Uh sure. My friend and I will be there.
>> Okay.
>> Asalam everyone. Thank you for coming.
Let me introduce to you PRU El invest
investment linking issue policy by
Predential Malaysia.
>> Guys, this is the policy I'll tell you
about.
>> It combines life protection, optional
medical coverage and investment for
long-term growth.
>> So is it like protection and savings?
Exactly. You are getting protection by
building financial value.
Here is the scope of coverage. Death or
total and permanent disability,
protection during unexpected events and
investment value based on chosen funds.
What are the benefits? Okay, the
benefits are financial security, uh
flexible premium, long-term investment,
and peace of mind.
>> And how about the exclusion? Just like
most policies which is suicide in early
years uh self-inflicted injury and
illegal activities.
Oh, no one explained like this before to
me.
I don't want my family burden because I
delay.
>> I waited too long. Don't be like me.
>> That means we are you elite English.
Protect now and grow later.
That sound like very good deal to do.
I'm in. I'm in. I'm in. I'm in. I'm in.
I'm in.
Let's get moving.
>> Okay.
Heat.